Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.asia [Admin.@YNG]
=The Demon=
=الشيطان=
=Episode 12=
=الحلقة 12=
All right.
حسنًا.
Let's hear your plan.
دعونا نسمع خطتك.
Your Highness genuinely cares about the world.
إن سموكم يهتم حقًا بالعالم.
Lately, Moyuan City has been saturated with a demonic presence…
في الآونة الأخيرة، أصبحت مدينة مويوان مشبعة بالوجود الشيطاني...
Enough.
كافٍ.
I don't care
لا أهتم
about the fate of the world.
حول مصير العالم.
All I want is Shen Wangchen.
كل ما أريده هو شين وانجشن.
If that's the case,
إذا كان الأمر كذلك،
then it's simple.
ثم الأمر بسيط.
It's you.
إنه أنت.
What are you doing in Moyuan City?
ماذا تفعل في مدينة مويوان؟
None of your business.
هذا ليس من شأنك.
Look who's talking.
انظر من يتكلم
Why were you on the roof
لماذا كنت على السطح؟
of Shen Wangchen's house?
من منزل شين وانغشن؟
I'm here to catch demons.
أنا هنا للقبض على الشياطين.
That's laughable.
هذا مضحك.
This is Shen Wangchen's home.
هذا هو منزل شين وانجشن.
Where are the demons?
أين الشياطين؟
- Don't tell me…
- لا تخبرني...
100 years ago,
منذ 100 عام،
demon slayers battled the Cat Demon for a long time
قاتل قاتلو الشياطين شيطان القط لفترة طويلة
and finally defeated her by the sword.
وأخيراً هزمها بالسيف.
She destroyed her demon core
لقد دمرت جوهر شيطانها
and turned to ash.
وتحولت إلى رماد.
(You)
(أنت)
(are that Cat Demon.)
(هل هذا القط شيطان؟)
(I don't understand.)
(لا أفهم.)
(I know she's a demon now,)
(أعلم أنها شيطانة الآن)
(but why do I find it even harder to strike her down?)
(ولكن لماذا أجد صعوبة أكبر في ضربها؟)
(What defines)
(ما الذي يحدد)
(good and evil?)
(الخير والشر؟)
(It seems I still haven't fully grasped)
(يبدو أنني لم أفهم الأمر بشكل كامل بعد)
(the notion)
(المفهوم)
(of right and wrong.)
(من الصواب والخطأ.)
Did you go after the Cat Demon?
هل ذهبت وراء شيطان القط؟
I was incompetent.
لقد كنت غير كفء.
I failed to catch the Cat Demon
لقد فشلت في القبض على شيطان القط
and even soiled the geomantic compass.
وحتى البوصلة الجيومانتية لوثت.
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
I ran into human traffickers.
لقد واجهت تجار البشر.
I got hurt while rescuing a child.
لقد تعرضت للأذى أثناء إنقاذ طفل.
Once the compass is stained with blood,
بمجرد أن تتلطخ البوصلة بالدماء،
it will only point to the blood's owner for seven days.
لن يشير إلا إلى صاحب الدم لمدة سبعة أيام.
Never mind.
لا تهتم.
Go treat your wounds.
اذهب لعلاج جروحك.
Understood.
مفهومة.
Master,
يتقن،
according to the servants,
وفقا للخدم،
Young Madam has been
لقد كانت السيدة الشابة
acting strange lately.
يتصرف بغرابة في الآونة الأخيرة.
Someone saw her drinking water
لقد رأى أحدهم أنها تشرب الماء
with her tongue.
مع لسانها.
She also likes to fish
كما أنها تحب الصيد
in your koi pond.
في بركة الكوي الخاصة بك.
Qianchun Mountain has fewer
جبل تشيان تشون لديه عدد أقل
than 20 hunting families.
أكثر من 20 عائلة صيد.
None with the surname Fan, as far as we know.
لا يوجد أحد يحمل لقب Fan، على حد علمنا.
Dear,
عزيزي،
that is peculiar indeed.
وهذا أمر غريب بالفعل.
All right, all right.
حسناً، حسناً.
I will investigate this matter.
سأحقق في هذا الأمر.
Zhen Gui,
تشن غوي,
there's another urgent task
هناك مهمة عاجلة أخرى
I need you to handle.
أحتاج إليك للتعامل معي.
Rumor has it a vicious demon
يقال أنه شيطان شرير
has been spotted again inside the city.
تم رصده مرة أخرى داخل المدينة.
Every place it visits,
كل مكان يزوره،
no one survives.
لا أحد ينجو.
The people are terrified.
الناس مرعوبون.
It looks like trouble is brewing in the city again.
يبدو أن المشاكل تختمر في المدينة مرة أخرى.
Find this demon's whereabouts
العثور على مكان وجود هذا الشيطان
and report to me.
وأبلغني.
Why are you standing there? Go!
لماذا تقف هناك؟ اذهب!
Though Qianchun Mountain is sparsely populated,
على الرغم من أن جبل تشيان تشون قليل السكان،
demons abound.
الشياطين كثيرة.
Dear, you mean…
عزيزي هل تقصد...
Chen has genuine feelings for her.
تشين لديه مشاعر حقيقية تجاهها.
Don't spread this
لا تنشر هذا
until we know the full truth.
حتى نعرف الحقيقة كاملة.
Otherwise,
خلاف ذلك،
it could hurt them both.
قد يؤذيهما كلاهما.
All right.
حسنًا.
What's this blackened thing?
ما هذا الشيء الأسود؟
Is that a charcoal stick?
هل هذه عصا الفحم؟
People say it tastes good.
يقول الناس أن طعمه جيد.
Who said that?
من قال ذلك؟
If you make anyone sick, you'll pay for it!
إذا تسببت في مرض أي شخص، فسوف تدفع ثمن ذلك!
It looks fine to me.
يبدو جيدا بالنسبة لي.
It's all burnt to charcoal!
لقد احترق كل شيء حتى تحول إلى فحم!
Who would eat
من يأكل؟
something that black?
شيء أسود؟
They're eating it.
إنهم يأكلونه.
They eat it?
هل يأكلونه؟
If they get sick, you'll pay!
إذا مرضوا فسوف تدفع الثمن!
Ever since Chief Fan showed up,
منذ ظهور رئيس المعجبين،
the red beans are being used up faster than ever.
يتم استهلاك الفاصوليا الحمراء بشكل أسرع من أي وقت مضى.
If this keeps up,
إذا استمر هذا،
we'll have to start buying them from outside the city.
سيتعين علينا أن نبدأ بشرائها من خارج المدينة.
It's perfectly fine!
إنه جيد تماما!
Jiang Li?
جيانغ لي؟
I finally found you, Jiang Li!
لقد وجدتك أخيرا، جيانغ لي!
They won't even let me fish anymore.
لن يسمحوا لي بالصيد بعد الآن.
Fishing like this takes forever…
إن الصيد بهذه الطريقة يستغرق وقتًا طويلاً ...
Dayao!
مع السلامة!
Quiet. I'm fishing.
هدوء. أنا أمارس الصيد.
Momo?
يكتب؟
Momo!
يكتب!
Dayao!
مع السلامة!
Oh,
أوه،
I missed you so much!
لقد افتقدتك كثيرا!
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
It's a long story.
إنها قصة طويلة.
You can move in and tell her everything later.
يمكنك الانتقال إليها وإخبارها بكل شيء لاحقًا.
Right.
يمين.
Come on.
تعال.
I'll give you a tour.
سأعطيك جولة.
All right.
حسنًا.
You managed to get here on your own.
لقد تمكنت من الوصول إلى هنا بمفردك.
Impressive.
بديع.
I'm amazing, aren't I?
أنا مذهلة، أليس كذلك؟
Not bad.
ليس سيئًا.
Dayao.
مع السلامة.
You two go on ahead.
اذهبوا للأمام.
All right.
حسنًا.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Come on.
تعال.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Do you remember I told you
هل تتذكر أنني قلت لك
there's a hidden hand
هناك يد خفية
stirring trouble behind the scenes,
إثارة المشاكل خلف الكواليس،
deliberately causing chaos
التسبب في الفوضى عمدًا
to pit humans and demons
لإثارة البشر والشياطين
against each other?
ضد بعضهم البعض؟
I've decided to take action
لقد قررت اتخاذ إجراء
and unravel their scheme piece by piece.
وكشف مخططهم قطعة قطعة.
During this time,
خلال هذا الوقت،
it might be dangerous for you and Rong Momo
قد يكون الأمر خطيرًا بالنسبة لك و رونغ مومو
to stay in the city.
للبقاء في المدينة.
Why don't you both
لماذا لا تفعلان كلاكما؟
go back to the fort
العودة إلى الحصن
for a while?
لفترة من الوقت؟
Dangerous?
خطير؟
Moyuan City?
مدينة مويوان؟
If you hadn't stopped me
لو لم توقفني
from acting,
من التمثيل،
I'd crush
سأسحق
those puny humans
هؤلاء البشر الضعفاء
like ants.
مثل النمل.
You worry too much.
أنت تقلق كثيرا.
Besides,
بجانب،
you said
أنت قلت
this is your territory.
هذه هي منطقتك.
You'll protect me.
سوف تحميني.
I'm afraid
انا خائف
I won't be able to protect you anymore.
لن أكون قادراً على حمايتك بعد الآن.
What does that mean?
ماذا يعني ذلك؟
I don't want to study today.
لا أريد أن أدرس اليوم.
I'm off to play with Rong Momo.
سأذهب للعب مع رونغ مومو.
Momo!
يكتب!
Dayao!
مع السلامة!
I'll show you
سأريك
something amazing!
شيئ مذهل!
All right!
حسنًا!
Listen,
يستمع،
there's a little girl who raises rabbits here,
هناك فتاة صغيرة تربي الأرانب هنا،
and she idolizes me.
وهي تعبدني.
So,
لذا،
humans aren't so bad after all.
البشر ليسوا سيئين على أية حال.
They admire us demons.
إنهم معجبون بنا نحن الشياطين.
So, humans
لذا، البشر
treat you well then?
هل يعاملك جيدا إذن؟
Very well.
جيد جدا.
Everything
كل شئ
requires strategy.
يتطلب استراتيجية.
I mean,
أعني،
my alliance with Shen Wangchen
تحالفي مع شين وانغتشين
worked perfectly.
عملت بشكل مثالي.
Dayao,
صباح الخير،
is your relationship with Mr. Shen
هل علاقتك بالسيد شين
just an alliance?
مجرد تحالف؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
And a very close one at that.
وواحدة قريبة جدًا في ذلك.
Whenever I find something tasty,
كلما وجدت شيئا لذيذا،
he's the first to try it.
إنه أول من جرب ذلك.
When I find something fun,
عندما أجد شيئا ممتعا،
he's the first one I tell.
إنه أول شخص أخبره.
Every night when we part,
كل ليلة عندما نفترق،
I feel
انا اشعر
so empty inside.
فارغ جداً من الداخل.
I can't wait for morning to come.
لا أستطيع الانتظار حتى يأتي الصباح.
He suggested I leave here just now.
لقد اقترح علي أن أغادر هنا الآن.
How could I?
كيف يمكنني ذلك؟
I'd be heartbroken.
سوف أكون حزينًا.
Dayao,
صباح الخير،
that's not strategy.
هذه ليست استراتيجية.
That's love.
هذا هو الحب.
♪How do you measure one's concern?♪
♪كيف تقيس اهتمامك؟♪
I'm in love with him?
هل أنا أحبه؟
Yes.
نعم.
♪Even an inch of it feels absurd♪
♪حتى بوصة واحدة منه تبدو سخيفة♪
♪Who comes with me on my long journey?♪
♪من يأتي معي في رحلتي الطويلة؟♪
♪Where can I rest after picking up the cold branches?♪
♪أين يمكنني أن أستريح بعد التقاط الأغصان الباردة؟♪
♪I'm willing to trade all my smiles from the past♪
♪أنا على استعداد لتبادل كل ابتساماتي من الماضي♪
♪In exchange for my weary face♪
♪في مقابل وجهي المتعب♪
♪In this restless world, who can walk away unscathed?♪
♪في هذا العالم المضطرب، من يستطيع أن يخرج منه دون أن يصاب بأذى؟♪
♪Alone under the fading moon, I bid you farewell♪
♪ وحدي تحت القمر الخافت، أودعك ♪
♪I'm willing to give from the cracks of my memory♪
♪أنا على استعداد للعطاء من شقوق ذاكرتي♪
♪To shatter the beauty of my youth♪
♪لتحطيم جمال شبابي♪
Shen Wangchen,
شين وانجشن,
I love you.
أحبك.
I've decided
لقد قررت
to propose to Princess Huaiyang.
للتقدم لخطبة الأميرة هوايانج.
♪Where did I lose my direction?♪
♪أين فقدت اتجاهي؟♪
♪Only emptiness is left♪
♪لم يبق سوى الفراغ♪
♪Restless, sleepless, we part ways♪
♪أرق، بلا نوم، افترقنا♪
♪As sorrow slowly grows within♪
♪كما ينمو الحزن ببطء في الداخل♪
♪Tears can't heal, smiles still ache♪
♪الدموع لا يمكن أن تشفى، والابتسامات لا تزال تؤلم♪
♪Because my heart's with you♪
♪لأن قلبي معك♪
♪Your gaze melted the haze♪
♪نظرتك أذابت الضباب♪
♪Waiting so long for your return♪
♪انتظر عودتك لفترة طويلة♪
♪The setting sun reminds me of you♪
♪تذكّرني الشمس الغاربة بك♪
♪If the clear sky is torn by storm and rain one day♪
♪إذا تمزقت السماء الصافية بالعاصفة والمطر يومًا ما♪
♪Tears will flow♪
♪الدموع سوف تتدفق♪
♪I will still wait here with no regrets♪
♪سوف أظل أنتظر هنا دون أي ندم♪
♪Waiting so long for your return♪
♪انتظر عودتك لفترة طويلة♪
♪The setting sun reminds me of you♪
♪تذكّرني الشمس الغاربة بك♪
♪In the amber desert, you turn away with tears in your eyes♪
♪في الصحراء الكهرمانية، تبتعد والدموع في عينيك♪
♪I'll welcome you back in a red dress♪
♪سأرحب بك مرة أخرى في ثوب أحمر♪
♪Waiting forever with no regrets♪
♪الانتظار إلى الأبد دون أي ندم♪